Forrest "Bud" Harris Photographs, ca. 1950s-2007 AIS.2013.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Slides, ca. 1960s-2003; IV.
  - Koppers; Alcoa: Slag Site; Koppers: Railroad; Cake; Text Slides; Railroad Pictures; "Switch the Stacks" (Railroad Track Wood) (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Koppers: Track Panel,; H-W; Hickson Corporation: Colorado (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - "The Sorter"; ITSCO; Budweiser and ITSCO; Railroad Tracks; Railwood; Railwood Being Treated; Small Portfolio; Funway Race; Health Works; Koppers: Highway Walls, 144 Truck Tires (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Koppers: Railroad Tracks and Track Laying Machine; Koppers: Aerial, Map, Somerville; Koppers: Heinz School, City in Background (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Koppers: Wood Treating Slideshow; South Side Drug and Alcohol Slideshow (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - South Side Drug and Alcohol Slideshow; Gateway Rehab Slideshow (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - IABC Talk; American Express Benefits Slideshow #1 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Koppers: Plants; Minolta CCE Test; American Express Auditor Slideshow #2 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - American Express Incentive Savings Plan Slideshow (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - American Express Incentive Savings Plan Slideshow; Historic Railroad Photos (not Bud's images); Train Panels; Koppers: ITSCO, St. Louis, Bud Yard (Budweiser Corporation); Koppers: Wood Treatment, Railroad Slideshow; Koppers: Railroad (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - American Express Incentive Savings Plan: Bud's Note (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Koppers: Wood Treatment; American Express Benefits Slideshow (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Notes (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Black and White Photos for Exhibition, ca. 1960s (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Fritz Goro, March 1964 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Three Rivers Stadium; Ken Ramsey People, ca. 1970s (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Tractors; Man by Model, June 1970 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Koppers: Columbus, Ohio; Gas Station: Marathon Oil; House of Wolman; Lite Risers, August 3, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - St. Peters, July 1973 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Social Security Administration, September 21, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 2-3)
  - Wightman Manor; Children, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Milltown; Walk Steel; Silent, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - La Normande Restaurant: Shoot for Business Week, August 1979 (Box 56, Folder 3-4)
    Manuscript page available.
  - IABC (International Association of Business Communicators) Entry, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - BMX, October 1981 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Koppers: Sales Presentation to Management Committee, April 25, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 4-5)
  - Sully Miller Contracting Company, November 1986 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Hickson Corporation Deck, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Print and negative also available.
  - Conn. Boomer, August 4, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Conn. NG, August 3, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Hickson Corporation, October 26, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Alcoa: Bob Cosgrove, October 27, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - PXS Slide Presentation to USA Cycling for Olympic Trials Consideration, 1995/1996; Not all photographs are Bud's, some are from other photographers. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Koppers, March 1996 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Hickson Corporation: Extras, October 17, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Thrift Drug Classic: Lance Armstrong finishing USA Champion Crossing Liberty Bridge, Start Line with Sophie et. al., 1996; Not all photographs taken by Bud. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Guthrie Fab Shop (Railroad), June 1998 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Koppers: Railroad, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Koppers: KSA Ties Becks Run Road, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Trees, Car, Storm Damage, May 16, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Pittsburgh City Snowstorm: Submarine and Barge, January 2003 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Koppers: Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad, September 2003 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Koppers: Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad, September 2003 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Black and White Slide Samples, March 9, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Moving Images, ca. 1960s-2000; V.
  Formats in this series include VHS, Beta, UMatic and Motion Picture Film. Topics include: Koppers, KSA, Tom Nypaver, The DuPont Seal Skinz, BMX, Panta Rhetoric, Joseph M. Katz Graduate School of Business, Keystone, Remsa, Philip Pelusi, Social Security Administration, Toyota, American Express, Outdoor Wood, The Joel Martin Show, J&L Steel, Pool Hall, Stainless Steel Gange, St. Peter's Home for Retarded Children, Gog Magog and Babylon, Kennywood, NASA, The Thoroughbred Connection, Dale Beachy, PPG, and Market Potential.
  - VHS, 1985-1997; 1. (Box 58-60)
    Subjects include: Koppers, KSA, Tom Nypaver, The DuPont Seal Skinz, BMX, "The Koppers Perspective," "The Railroad Partner," Panta Rhetoric, Joseph M. Katz Graduate School of Business, Keystone, Remsa, Philip Pelusi, Social Security Administration: "Our Man in Your Hometown," Market Potential: "Saginaw Rail Footage," Serve Program, Toyota, and American Express.
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner", September 1997 (Box 58, Video 1)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner" (Box 58, Video 2)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Revised, August 20, 1997 (Box 58, Video 3)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Reel 7 & 8, Roanoke, Virginia, August 14, 1995 (Box 58, Video 4)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Reel 11, Guthrie, Oklahoma, August 16, 1995 (Box 58, Video 5)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Reel 12, Guthrie, Oklahoma, August 16, 1995 (Box 58, Video 53)
    - Koppers: KSA Reel 1, 2, 4, 6 (Box 58, Video 6)
    - Koppers: REMSA KSA, August 27, 1997 (Box 58, Video 7-8)
    - Koppers: REMSA KSA, 1993 (Box 58, Video 9)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partners" Revised, with Creosote, April 11, 1996 (Box 58, Video 10, 23)
    - Koppers: Railroad Tracks, Nebraska, June 4, 1993 (Box 58, Video 11)
    - Koppers: KSA "Rail Atlanta" Field Footage, ca. 1990s (Box 58, Video 12)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner" Reels 16, 17, 18, Portsmouth, New Hampshire, ca. 1990s (Box 58, Video 13)
    - The DuPont SealSkinz Story Sales Guide, 1995 (Box 58, Video 14)
    - BMX Promotion Tape, Columbus, Ohio, 1994 (Box 58, Video 15)
    - Koppers: Susquehanna Cogeneration Facility, ca. 1990s (Box 58, Video 16)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Reels 14-16, Susquehanna and Black, ca. 1990s (Box 58, Video 17)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Susquehanna and Portsmouth, New Hampshire, ca. 1990s (Box 58, Video 18)
    - Koppers: Roanoke, Virginia (Box 58, Video 19)
    - REMSA: Final Edit Master (Box 58, Video 20)
    - Allegheny Policy Council: Career and Academic Passport (Box 58, Video 21)
    - Koppers: "Commitment to Quality" (Box 58, Video 22)
    - Koppers: Annual Shareholders Meeting/Koppers Commitment to Quality, 1987 (Box 58, Video 24)
    - Koppers: Guthrie and Little Rock Plants, 1997 (Box 58, Video 25)
    - Koppers: "The Koppers Perspective", May 14, 1985 (Box 58, Video 26)
    - Koppers: Offline, Revised, July 14, 1997 (Box 58, Video 27)
    - Koppers: Up To Now (Box 58, Video 28)
    - Koppers: Serve Program, Heritage, Benefits, Koppers Perspective (Box 58, Video 29)
    - Heinz History Center: Sports History Museum (Box 58, Video 30)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner" Somerville, Massachusetts, August 21, 1995 (Box 58, Video 31)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner" Guthrie, Oklahoma, August 16, 1995 (Box 58, Video 32)
    - REMSA, August 18, 1997 (Box 58, Video 33)
    - NRCA Presentation: Ohbayashi, Giffels Associates, February 10, 1988 (Box 58, Video 34)
    - Koppers: "Railroad Partner" Revised, August 18, 1997 (Box 59, Video 35)
    - Panta Rhetoric Demo (Box 59, Video 36)
    - Koppers: Concrete Ties and Crossings, ca. 1990s (Box 59, Video 37)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner" Somerville, Massachusetts, August 21, 1995 (Box 59, Video 38)
    - Wastebusters Central (Box 59, Video 39)
    - Koppers (Box 59, Video 40, 42-43, 46-47, 49, 65-66)
    - Philip Pelusi Washington Shoot (Box 59, Video 41)
    - Koppers: Rail Crossings, Truck Crossings, KSA Trade Show, 1997 (Box 59, Video 44)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner" Somerville and Galesburg, ca. 1990s (Box 59, Video 45)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," (Safety Glass Animation), February 14, 1996 (Box 59, Video 48)
    - Koppers: Concrete Ties (Box 59, Video 50)
    - Saganaw Switch Ties Train, August 13, 1993 (Box 59, Video 51)
    - KSA Offline, January 21, 1997 (Box 59, Video 52)
    - Market Potential, May 21, 1993 (Box 59, Video 54)
    - Koppers: "Under One Roof at Koppers", June 1988 (Box 59, Video 55)
    - Koppers: "Third Annual Quality Day, an Overview" (Box 59, Video 56)
    - Koppers: Bud's Speech at Quality Day Three, April 29, 1987 (Box 59, Video 57)
    - Koppers: Quality Day Three, April 29, 1987 (Box 59, Video 58)
    - Koppers: Serve Program, February 11, 1985 (Box 59, Video 59)
    - Toyota (Box 59, Video 60)
    - Koppers: Healthy, Wealthy and Wise Employee Savings Plan, January 27, 1984 (Box 59, Video 61)
    - Koppers: "The Koppers Perspective", May 14, 1985 (Box 59, Video 62)
    - Koppers: Benefits for You (Box 59, Video 63)
    - Koppers: Offline, October 1995 (Box 59, Video 64)
    - American Express (Box 59, Video 67-70)
    - Tom Loadman Interviews, October 13, 1995 (Box 59, Video 71)
    - On Location, January 1980 (Box 59, Video 72)
    - Social Security Administration: "Our Man in your Hometown", February 1, 2000 (Box 60, Video 73)
    - Social Security Administration: "Our Man in your Hometown" (Long Version) (Box 60, Video 74)
    - KSA: Concrete Railroad Crossings, April 16, 1997 (Box 60, Video 75)
    - KSA: Concrete Railroad Crossing, Offline (Rough Cut), January 22, 1997 (Box 60, Video 76)
    - KSA REMSA, August 27, 1997 (Box 60, Video 77)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner" (Box 60, Video 78)
    - REMSA Trade Show, Market Potential: Crane Footage, Vazda, 1993 (Box 60, Video 79)
    - Koppers: REMSA, Rough Cut, August 5, 1997 (Box 60, Video 80)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner" Follansbee Plant, Wyoming, February 23, 1996 (Box 60, Video 81)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Roanoke, Virginia, August 15, 1995 (Box 60, Video 82)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Interviews, ca. 1990s (Box 60, Video 83)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Guthrie, Oklahoma, August 16, 1995 (Box 60, Video 84)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Test Edit of Creasote Add, March 8, 1996 (Box 60, Video 85)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," First Rough Cut, August 24, 1995 (Box 60, Video 86)
    - Koppers: Offline, "Railroad Partner", July 8, 1997 (Box 60, Video 87)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partners," Galesburg, Illinois, ca. 1990s (Box 60, Video 88)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Roanoke, Virginia, August 14, 1995 (Box 60, Video 89)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Roll 20, VO, ca. 1990s (Box 60, Video 90)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Roll 19, ca. 1990s (Box 60, Video 91)
    - Koppers: Interivews #3, October 16, 1995 (Box 60, Video 92)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Reel 9&10, Roanoke, Virginia, August 15, 1995 (Box 60, Video 93)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Reel 1&2, Time Code Burns, ca. 1990s (Box 60, Video 94)
  - Beta, 1993-2000; 2.
    Subjects include: Social Security Administration: "Our Man in Our Hometown," Koppers: "The Railroad's Partner" with reels from Atlanta, Somerville, Galesburg, Roanoke, Guthrie, Susquehanna, and Little Rock, NASA, The Thoroughbred Connection, Dale Beachy, PPG, Market Potential and KSA.
    - KSA: "Rail Atlanta", April 28, 1993 (Box 61, Video 1)
    - Market Potential: Crane Footage (Box 61, Video 2)
    - GE: AC Locomotive Aerials (Box 61, Video 3)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad's Partner," Somerville Plant, Galesburg, Roanoke, Guthrie, Susquehanna, Portsmouth, 1995 (Box 61, Video 5-24)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad's Partner," Follansbee, West Virginia, February 23, 1996 (Box 61, Video 30)
    - Koppers: "Coal Tar Built-Up Roofing", October 1, 1996 (Box 61, Video 31-32)
    - Koppers: "Coal Tar Built-Up Roofing", October 4, 1996 (Box 61, Video 33-34)
    - KSA Concrete Crossing, October 2, 1996 (Box 61, Video 35-39)
    - KSA: Lab Shots, November 1996 (Box 61, Video 40-41)
    - KSA: Lab Shots, November 1996 (Box 62, Video 42)
    - KSA: Dale Beachy, Rail Crossings, Louisiana, April 9, 1997 (Box 62, Video 43)
    - Koppers: Guthrie, Kentucky, June 1997 (Box 62, Video 44-46)
    - Koppers: Little Rock, Arkansas, June 1997 (Box 62, Video 47-48)
    - Koppers: Labs, June 1997 (Box 62, Video 49-51)
    - Koppers: Photos, ca. 1990s (Box 62, Video 52)
    - Koppers: Work, ca. 1990s (Box 62, Video 55)
    - KSA Railroad Tie Plant, May 13, 1993 (Box 62, Video 58-61)
    - Norfolk Southern Corporation: The Thoroughbred Connection, 1994 (Box 62, Video 62)
    - IISI Steel Material for the Future, June 16, 1997 (Box 62, Video 63)
    - NASA: Go for Eva, September 1993 (Box 62, Video 64)
    - Koppers: Railroad Hammer, ca. 1990s (Box 62, Video 65)
    - PPG, June 24, 1997 (Box 62, Video 66)
    - KSA REMSA, Mixed Audio, Edit Master, August 27, 1997 (Box 62, Video 67)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Revised, Edited Master, August 19, 1997 (Box 62, Video 68)
    - Social Security Administration: "Our Man in Your Hometown", February 1, 2000 (Box 62, Video 69)
    - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner," Safety Glass Animation, February 14, 1996 (Box 62, Video 70)
    - Social Security Administration: "Our Man in your Hometown" (Box 62, Video 71)
  - UMatic, ca. 1960s-1985; 3.
    Subjects include: Outdoor Wood, Koppers, The Social Security Administration, Motocross, American Express, and The Joel Martin Show.
    - Outdoor Wood: Wolmanized Pressure Treated Lumber, Huck, ca. 1970s (Box 63, Video 1)
    - Kopper: Samples, ca. 1970s (Box 63, Video 2)
    - Social Security Administration: "Our Man in your Hometown", ca. 1960s (Box 63, Video 3, 7)
    - Koppers: Washington D.C. Interview, Nila, Communications, 1976 (Box 63, Video 4)
    - Nila Vehar, Washington D.C., National Planning, 1976 (Box 63, Video 5)
    - Motocross Championship, 1977 (Box 63, Video 6)
    - American Express: "Intern Program" and "Credit Card Program", ca. 1970s (Box 63, Video 8)
    - American Express: On Location, Fourth Edition, April 1980 (Box 63, Video 9)
    - American Express: "Pilot Program," Time Coded Original Material, 1978-1979 (Box 63, Video 10)
    - American Express: "On Location," Fourth Edition, 1980 (Box 63, Video 11)
    - Koppers: History and Employees Benefits Overview, February 1, 1985 (Box 63, Video 12)
    - American Express: Time Coded Original Material, Reel 1, ca. 1970s (Box 63, Video 13)
    - American Express: "On Location," New Orleans and Phoenix, ca. 1970s (Box 64, Video 14)
    - American Express: On Location, Third Edition, January 1980 (Box 64, Video 15)
    - American Express: "Awards," Edit Master, ca. 1970s (Box 64, Video 16)
    - American Express: " Program Pilot," Time Coded Original Material, 1978 (Box 64, Video 17)
    - American Express: Time Coded Original Material, ca. 1970s (Box 64, Video 18)
    - ICP Promo, 1990 (Box 64, Video 19)
    - Bud Harris Sample: Social Security Administration Story, ca. 1960s-1970s (Box 64, Video 20)
    - Koppers: "All Weather Wood Foundation", ca. 1970s-1980s (Box 64, Video 21)
    - Koppers: "All Weather Wood Foundation Show", ca. 1970s-1980s (Box 64, Video 22)
    - Koppers: "Serve" Program, ca. 1970s-1980s (Box 64, Video 23)
    - Koppers: "KMM" and "Dycon Concrete", ca. 1970s-1980s (Box 64, Video 24)
  - Motion Picture Film, 1968-1980; 4.
    Subjects include: Koppers, Social Security Administration, J&L Steel, Pool Hall, Stainless Steel Gange, St. Peter's Home for Retarded Children, Gog Magog and Babylon, Kennywood, and the Boy Scouts of America.
    - Koppers Co., October 2, 1972 (Box 65, Reel 1)
    - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, September 29, 1972 (Box 65, Reel 2)
    - Koppers: Wolman, Lex. Park., October 10, 1972 (Box 65, Reel 3)
    - Koppers: Wolman, November 14, 1972 (Box 65, Reel 3)
    - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, Original Footage (Box 65, Reel 4)
    - Koppers, March 31, 1972 (Box 65, Reel 5-8)
    - Social Security Administration: Our Man in Your Hometown (Box 65, Reel 9)
    - Social Security Administration: Our Man in Your Hometown, Entry for Award for Communications Excellence Award, 1975 (Box 66, Reel 10)
    - J&L Steel L.A.M. Process (Box 66, Reel 11)
    - Kennywood: Black and White, Silent (Box 66, Reel 12)
    - J&L Steel: Stainless Steel Cleanliness. Color Optical Audio. Bud Harris Narrates, 1968 (Box 66, Reel 13)
    - J&L Steel: Stainless Pickling. Optical Audio, Color (Box 66, Reel 14)
    - Koppers: Wolman, "Wood Foundation", June 15, 1975 (Box 66, Reel 15)
    - Koppers: Bulk Materials Reclaimer Systems. Silent, Bud Harris on Camera (Box 66, Reel 16)
    - Koppers: "The Koppers Perspective," by MRG Productions (Box 66, Reel 17)
    - Pool Hall Exhibition. Black and White, Silent (Box 66, Reel 18)
    - J&L: Stainless Steel Refinement. Color, Optical Audio, Bud Harris Narrates, 1968 (Box 66, Reel 19)
    - J&L: Graham Lab, Stainless Steel: 304 N Testing, 1968 (Box 66, Reel 20)
    - Steel, Color Silent (Box 66, Reel 21)
    - Stainless Steel Gange. Bad Audio (Optical), Color, 1968 (Box 66, Reel 22)
    - J&L: Stainless Steel Refinement. Color, Optical Audio. Bud Harris Narrates, 1968 (Box 66, Reel 23)
    - J&L Steel: Trade Show, Promotion, January 1980 (Box 66, Reel 24)
    - Koppers: Wood House (Box 66, Reel 25)
    - St. Peters Home for Retarded Children (Box 66, Reel 26)
    - Gog, Magog and Babylon, 1960 (Box 66, Reel 27)
      Full length film, 30 minutes.
    - Boy Scouts of America Public Service Announcements, 1973-1974 (Box 66, Reel 28)
- DVDs, ca. 1990s-2000s; VI.
  This collection of DVDs includes films made by Harris as well as an interview with a local television station.
  - Lynne Hayes-Freeland Show with Bud Harris and George Barber, January 14, 2007 (Audio-cabinet 5, Drawer 6, Disk 1-2)
  - Koppers: "The Railroad Partner", ca. 1990s (Audio-cabinet 5, Drawer 6, Disk 3-4)
  - Social Security Administration: "Our Man in Your Hometown", ca. 1990s (Audio-cabinet 5, Drawer 6, Disk 5)
  - American Express: Intern Training Program, 2007 (Audio-cabinet 5, Drawer 6, Disk 6)
- Audio, 1976-1980; VII.
  All audio in this series are on audio cassette tapes. Subjects include: Southside Drug and Alcohol, Gateway Rehabilitation Center, American Express, Audio Notes, Social Security Administration, Out of Office Messages, Koppers, Association of National Advertisers and Elliot Carson.
  - B-1 Foreclosure, February 20, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 1, 6)
  - Elliot Carson Recorded Phone Call, Bud: Pressure Point Analysis (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - American Express: Vero Computer Terminal, Background Glass, Simulated Interivew, September 1978 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - B-2, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - B-2 Foreclosure, February 29, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - B-5, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Southside Drug and Alcohol Slideshow Audio (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Gateway Rehabilitation Center Slideshow Audio (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Original Gateway Interviews: Alcoholism, 3 Music Cuts (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - American Express Employee Benefit Program (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - American Express Employee Benefits Slide Show (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Bud Audio Notes to Himself, Thoughts on Survival Service (Not Bud) (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Social Security Administration Interview, ca. 1960s-1970s (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Bud's Out of Office Message (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - AM Shooting Pitt, Second Draft (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Koppers: Playground Music, September 22, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Koppers: Employee Benefit Road Show, May 30, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - American Express: Corporate Audit Training, October 1979 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - American Express: Audit Training Program Revised, October 26, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - American Express: Audit Training Program, On Location, November 5, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - American Express: Corporate Audit Training, January 26, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Association of National Advertisers, John Naisbitt, September 30, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Manuscripts, ca. 1960s-2007; VIII.
  Included in this series are photographer's log books, billing books, invoice journals, appointment books, address books, documents pertaining to Harris's time working at Koppers, resumes, published work, correspondence, business papers, and exhibition information. The majority of this series is text, though some magazines are included with reproductions of Harris's work.
  - Photo Log Books, 1.
    - Log Books, Billing Books, Financial Records, Invoices, Day Books and Appointment Books, 1971-1990 (Box 71-72)
  - Address Books and Planners, 2.
    - Planners, 1979-1997 (Box 72, Folder 16-17)
    - Planners, 1969-2005 (Box 73-74)
    - Address Book, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Address Books, 1979-2005 (Box 73)
  - Business Papers and Published Work, 3.
    - Photo Maxima Envelope, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Photo Maxima Correspondence, March 21, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Social Security Administration Correspondence, 1969,1971 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Social Security Administration: Catalog of Photographs for SSA Use, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Business Papers: Rutgers, ca. 1970s (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Europe, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Documentary People Photo Essay Proposal, ca. 1970s (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Christian Fisher Correspondence (about Europe Trip), August 8, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Social Security Administration: Program Circular, December 1, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Communication Arts: Vol. 12, No. 5, Ace Awards Catalog, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - "The Architecture of Peter Berndtson", 1971 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - AMAX Corporation Film Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Medical World News, 1972, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Burson-Marsteller International (About WABCO), August 11, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - IABC (International Association of Business Communicators), September 19, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - IABC Talk, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - AMEX "Only the Size is the Same" Information Packet (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - AMEX, Disney Project (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Business Week Correspondence, May 21, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - WTAE TV, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Pittsburgh Magazine: Panther Hollow Story, October 1988 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Alcoa: Paperwork, Correspondence, ca. 1990s (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Archadeck, 1992, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Archadeck, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Archadeck: Pamphlets and Correspondence, February 1, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Hickson Corporation Deck, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Alcoa: Annual Report, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Crossties Magazine, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Exhibition Correspondence, 1984, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 28)
      Subjects include: Rodef Shalom Brotherhood Show, Three Rivers Arts Festival, Bud's Resume for Rodef Shalom Show.
    - SMC Communications Committee Meeting, February 18, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - SMC Communications Committee Meeting, April 21, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Heinz History Center/ Western Pennsylvania Sports Museum, 2004-2006 (Box 76, Folder 31)
    - "Talking Steel Towns" Book by Ellie Wymard, Photographs by Bud, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 32)
    - Published Work, ca. 1960s-2004 (Box 76, Folder 33-36)